// array with questions

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who was the master of Darth Sidious (Emperor Palpatine)?",
        answer: "Darth Plagueis",
        options: [
            "Darth Tyranus",
            "Darth Plagueis",
            "Darth Vader",
            "Darth Maul",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What's the name of Boba Fett's ship?",
        answer: "Slave I.",
        options: [
            "Slave I.",
            "Millenium Falcon",
            "Malevolence",
            "Hound's tooth",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who was Anakin's Skywalker's padawan?",
        answer: "Ashoka Tano",
        options: [
            "Barriss Offee",
            "Cal Kestis",
            "Ashoka Tano",
            "Ezra Bridger",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What planet did Anakin Skywalker loose his legs and arm on?",
        answer: "Mustafar",
        options: [
            "Geonosis",
            "Coruscant",
            "Tatooine",
            "Mustafar",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What name did Obi-Wan Kenobi go by after the events of order 66?",
        answer: "Ben Kenobi",
        options: [
            "Ben Kenobi",
            "John Kenobi",
            "Bob Kenobi",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Lightsabers are powered by what type of crystal?",
        answer: "Kyber crystal",
        options: [
            "Light crystal",
            "Nova crystal",
            "Kyber crystal",
            "Force crystal",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the name of a clone that led the 501st Legion during the Clone Wars?",
        answer: "Captain Rex",
        options: [
            "Commander Cody",
            "Commander Wolf",
            "Captain Gregor",
            "Captain Rex",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What species is Chewbacca?",
        answer: "Wookie",
        options: [
            "Twi'lek",
            "Wookie",
            "Trandoshan",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the name of the female member of the Jedi High Council who is of the same species as Yoda?",
        answer: "Yaddle",
        options: [
            "Yaddle",
            "Grogu",
            "Ki-Adi-Mundi",
            "Shaak Ti",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What was the name of the creature that Boba Fett fell into?",
        answer: "Sarlacc",
        options: [
            "Acklay",
            "Rancor",
            "Sarlacc",
            "Mythosaur",
        ]
    },
];